Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Starlit Bloom=
=ازهار النجوم=
=Episode 6=
=الحلقة 6=
Mr. Xingchen,
السيد شينغتشن،
today I'll give you your first lesson
اليوم سأعطيك درسنا الأول
on the basics of corporate business management.
حول أساسيات إدارة الأعمال للشركات.
I hope you'll pay attention.
آمل أن تنتبهوا.
For fundamental business theories,
بالنسبة لنظريات الأعمال الأساسية،
through learning macroeconomics,
من خلال تعلم الاقتصاد الكلي،
you'll learn how fundamental theories affect business,
ستتعلم كيف تؤثر النظريات الأساسية على الأعمال التجارية،
so you can make an economic outlook in advance when doing strategic planning.
حتى تتمكن من وضع توقعات اقتصادية مسبقًا عند القيام بالتخطيط الاستراتيجي.
So,
لذا،
do you know what an "economic outlook" means?
هل تعلم ماذا يعني "التوقعات الاقتصادية"؟
Why would I need you if I did?
لماذا أحتاج إليك إذا كنت بحاجة إليك؟
Carry on.
حمل.
The project we developed together with the environmental agency
المشروع الذي قمنا بتطويره بالتعاون مع الوكالة البيئية
generated five revenue growth points last year.
حققت الشركة خمس نقاط نمو في الإيرادات العام الماضي.
Macroeconomics is about
الاقتصاد الكلي يتعلق بـ
understanding how the economy affects business activity.
فهم كيفية تأثير الاقتصاد على النشاط التجاري.
Economic management
الإدارة الاقتصادية
and the macroeconomic cycle are both essential.
والدورة الاقتصادية الكلية كلاهما ضروريان.
There's a key point about macroeconomics in relation to the two.
هناك نقطة رئيسية حول الاقتصاد الكلي فيما يتعلق بالاثنين.
Do you know what it is?
هل تعرف ما هو؟
♪My breath clutches my throat♪
♪أنفاسي تخنق حلقي♪
♪I barely made it through today♪
♪لقد تمكنت بالكاد من تجاوز اليوم♪
(What are you doing, Gu Liusu?)
(ماذا تفعل يا قو ليوسو؟)
So, the practical theories we learned earlier
لذا، فإن النظريات العملية التي تعلمناها سابقًا
are the most important.
هي الأكثر أهمية.
I hope you'll study them well.
آمل أن تدرسهم جيدا.
Macroeconomics in relation to economic management and the business cycle...
الاقتصاد الكلي وعلاقته بالإدارة الاقتصادية والدورة الاقتصادية
Is this what I taught you today?
هل هذا ما علمتك إياه اليوم؟
Give it back.
أعيدها.
(Collaboration Design Project)
(مشروع تصميم تعاوني)
♪Even hard to measure♪
♪حتى من الصعب قياسه♪
♪A trauma I wish to run away from♪
♪صدمة أتمنى الهروب منها♪
Hey.
يا.
Gu Liusu.
قو ليوسو.
(What's wrong with Lu Xingchen?)
(ما هو الخطأ مع لو شينغتشن؟)
Boss.
رئيس.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Why haven't you replied for days?
لماذا لم ترد منذ أيام؟
I have an idea.
عندي فكرة.
I figured out the design.
لقد توصلت إلى التصميم.
I'll tell you when you get back.
سأخبرك عندما تعود.
Gu Liusu.
قو ليوسو.
Why aren't you answering me?
لماذا لا تجيبني؟
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
(Hey, why am I laughing?)
(مهلا، لماذا أضحك؟)
(Lu Xingchen is Tang Baozhu's stepson.)
(لو Xingchen هو ابن ربيب Tang Baozhu.)
Gu Liusu.
قو ليوسو.
Why aren't you answering me?
لماذا لا تجيبني؟
All the companies attending the meeting rank among the top ten in the city.
جميع الشركات التي تحضر الاجتماع مصنفة ضمن العشرة الأوائل في المدينة.
Mr. Lu's very pleased that you came.
السيد لو سعيد جدًا بتواجدك.
He asked me to assist you.
لقد طلب مني مساعدتك.
(Are you sure Gu Liusu is back from the trip?)
(هل أنت متأكد من أن Gu Liusu عاد من الرحلة؟)
(Of course.)
(بالطبع.)
(My bestie would definitely let me know as soon as she's back.)
(صديقتي العزيزة ستخبرني بالتأكيد بمجرد عودتها.)
I'm going to the bathroom first.
سأذهب إلى الحمام أولاً.
You're right, Mr. Lin.
أنت على حق، السيد لين.
- I think we're missing someone. - Missing someone?
- أعتقد أننا نفتقد شخصًا ما. - هل نفتقد شخصًا ما؟
How could she be late for such an important meeting?
كيف يمكنها أن تتأخر عن اجتماع مهم كهذا؟
Are you talking about me, Mr. Lin?
هل تتحدث عني يا سيد لين؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
My flight was late.
كانت رحلتي في وقت متأخر.
This is an important event.
هذا حدث مهم .
Why are you dressed so scantily?
لماذا ترتدي ملابس قليلة جداً؟
Are you saying I'm underdressed
هل تقول أنني أرتدي ملابس غير مناسبة؟
or that I look good?
أو أني أبدو جيدا؟
Please button up, Mr. Lin.
من فضلك أغلق الأزرار، السيد لين.
Cover your big belly.
قم بتغطية بطنك الكبيرة.
Today's meeting
اجتماع اليوم
concerns the city's image.
يتعلق الأمر بصورة المدينة.
It doesn't really have anything to do with fashion, does it?
ليس له علاقة بالموضة حقًا، أليس كذلك؟
Why not
ولم لا
have our company take charge of it?
هل تتولى شركتنا المسؤولية عن ذلك؟
Anyone capable is welcome to compete.
أي شخص قادر على المنافسة هو موضع ترحيب.
It'd be best to transform the scenic spot into a large commercial complex
سيكون من الأفضل تحويل المكان الخلاب إلى مجمع تجاري كبير
and bring in shopping malls and luxury hotels.
وجلب مراكز التسوق والفنادق الفاخرة.
If we do that, the tourists' impression on our city culture
إذا فعلنا ذلك، فإن انطباع السائحين عن ثقافة مدينتنا
will remain only superficial.
سوف تبقى سطحية فقط.
We're not saints.
نحن لسنا قديسين.
We need to make money.
نحن بحاجة لكسب المال.
We are businesspeople.
نحن رجال أعمال.
I agree with commercialization,
أنا أوافق على التسويق التجاري،
but it should complement, not dominate.
ولكن ينبغي أن يكون مكملاً، وليس مسيطراً.
Ms. Gu,
السيدة جو،
no wonder you're a businesswoman.
فلا عجب أنك سيدة أعمال.
Why pull that long face all day,
لماذا تسحب هذا الوجه الطويل طوال اليوم،
like a Persian cat?
مثل القط الفارسي؟
That's just my face.
هذا مجرد وجهي.
Boring.
ممل.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
This idea
هذه الفكرة
is wonderful,
رائع
but it's too idealistic.
لكنها مثالية للغاية.
I understand you value economic benefits.
أنا أفهم أنك تقدر الفوائد الاقتصادية.
But we can't focus only on short-term gains
ولكن لا يمكننا التركيز فقط على المكاسب قصيرة الأجل
and lose the chance to build the city's soul, right?
وتفقد فرصة بناء روح المدينة، أليس كذلك؟
Culture is something you can't see or touch.
الثقافة هي شيء لا يمكنك رؤيته أو لمسه.
How can it sustain a project this big?
كيف يمكن دعم مشروع بهذا الحجم؟
Have you really considered everything, Ms. Gu?
هل فكرتِ حقًا في كل شيء، يا آنسة جو؟
Mr. Lin has a point.
السيد لين لديه نقطة.
Yeah. I agree with him.
نعم، أنا أتفق معه.
Mr. Lin is far-sighted indeed.
إن السيد لين بعيد النظر بالفعل.
Right.
يمين.
Oh, Mr. Lin.
أوه، السيد لين.
I was wondering which Mr. Lin it was.
كنت أتساءل أي السيد لين كان.
Turns out it's that Mr. Lin
اتضح أن السيد لين هو
who hired trolls to bash GL.
الذين استأجروا المتصيدين لمهاجمة GL.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Let me introduce you.
دعني أقدمك.
Mr. Lu,
السيد لو،
representing Xinghan Group at this meeting.
ممثل مجموعة شينغهان في هذا الاجتماع.
I'm just Mr. Lu Junior.
أنا فقط السيد لو جونيور.
Mr. Lin Xiang,
السيد لين شيانغ،
I wonder
انا اتعجب
if you're unhappy with Ms. Gu's proposal,
إذا كنت غير راضٍ عن اقتراح السيدة جو،
or if Xinyi Jewelry
أو إذا كانت مجوهرات شينيي
and GL
و GL
have some irreconcilable conflict?
هل لديك بعض الصراعات التي لا يمكن حلها؟
Ms. Gu runs a fashion brand,
السيدة جو تدير علامة تجارية للأزياء،
and I own a time-honored gold brand.
وأنا أملك علامة تجارية ذهبية عريقة.
We're in different lines of business. Why would there be any grudges?
نحن في مجالين مختلفين، فلماذا نحمل ضغائن؟
That sounds nice.
هذا يبدو لطيفا.
But I have a contract
ولكن لدي عقد
Mr. Lin Xiang signed
السيد لين شيانغ وقع
with a marketing account.
مع حساب تسويقي.
It concerns
إنه يتعلق
how to smear a rising brand,
كيفية تشويه سمعة علامة تجارية ناشئة
GL.
ج.ل.
Would you like
هل ترغب في ذلك؟
to take a look together?
لنلقي نظرة معًا؟
Young lad,
شاب صغير،
I won't argue with you for being rude.
لن أجادل معك لكونك وقحًا.
But you're talking nonsense.
لكنك تتحدث هراء.
You!
أنت!
How would Xinyi Jewelry stoop to such lowly tricks?
كيف يمكن لمجوهرات Xinyi أن تنحدر إلى مثل هذه الحيل المتواضعة؟
Lowly tricks?
حيل وضيعة؟
Fine.
بخير.
Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
you may pay them
يمكنك أن تدفع لهم
to keep their mouths shut.
ليُبقوا أفواههم مغلقة.
But if I pay them a little more,
ولكن إذا دفعت لهم أكثر قليلا،
do you think they'd still keep your secret?
هل تعتقد أنهم سيحتفظون بسرّك؟
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
The media is outside.
وسائل الإعلام في الخارج.
If I swing this door open,
إذا فتحت هذا الباب،
whether Xinyi Jewelry starts trending online or not,
سواء بدأت مجوهرات Xinyi في الانتشار عبر الإنترنت أم لا،
I can't say.
لا أستطيع أن أقول.
Mr. Mo,
السيد مو
is Xinghan really left in the hands
هل شينغهان حقا في أيدي
of this wet-behind-the-ears kid?
من هذا الطفل الرطب خلف الأذنين؟
Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
since Mr. Xingchen is representing Xinghan at this meeting,
نظرًا لأن السيد شينغتشين يمثل شينغهان في هذا الاجتماع،
he has the right...
لديه الحق...
I'm representing Xinghan.
أنا أمثل شينغان.
Nor am I back at Xinghan.
وأنا لم أعود إلى شينغهان.
I just can't sit by and watch it go to waste.
لا أستطيع الجلوس ومشاهدة الأمر يذهب سدى.
Our city has a unique history and culture.
مدينتنا لها تاريخ وثقافة فريدة من نوعها.
If we build on that and integrate it with cultural tourism,
إذا بنينا على ذلك ودمجناه مع السياحة الثقافية،
we can attract tourists with stronger spending power.
يمكننا جذب السياح الذين لديهم القدرة الشرائية الأقوى.
But look at you.
ولكن انظر إليك.
You form cliques for your own interests
تشكلون مجموعات من أجل مصالحكم الخاصة
and cast the city's development aside.
وتجاهل تطور المدينة.
Very well said.
قيل بشكل جيد للغاية.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
I have another meeting.
عندي اجتماع آخر.
I'll leave you to it.
سأتركك لذلك.
Ms. Gu,
السيدة جو،
if you ever need help,
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى المساعدة في أي وقت،
just let us know.
فقط اسمح لنا أن نعرف.
See you, Mr. Lin.
أراك لاحقا، السيد لين.
Take care, Mr. Lin.
اعتني بنفسك، سيد لين.
I was puzzled
لقد كنت في حيرة
how a post from Shi Yue's Weibo account with fewer than 2,000 followers
كيف يمكن لمنشور من حساب شي يو على Weibo الذي لديه أقل من 2000 متابع
could cause a stir.
قد يسبب ضجة.
It proves I was being used.
لقد أثبت أنني كنت أستخدم.
It really was Xinyi behind it.
لقد كان شينيي حقا وراء ذلك.
How could I not have seen it?
كيف لم ارى ذلك؟
How did you get this?
كيف حصلت على هذا؟
The power of money.
قوة المال.
I helped you.
لقد ساعدتك.
You don't thank me,
أنت لا تشكرني
and now you're taking my thing.
والآن أنت تأخذ الشيء الخاص بي.
You should thank yourself.
ينبغي عليك أن تشكر نفسك.
You cleared yourself of the suspicion of being involved with Xinyi.
لقد برأت نفسك من الشكوك حول تورطك مع شينيي.
Why pull me?
لماذا تسحبني؟
You haven't checked my assignment yet, Gu Liusu.
لم تقم بفحص مهمتي بعد، جو ليوسو.
Here's your drink.
هذا مشروبك
That old man Lin Xiang
هذا الرجل العجوز لين شيانغ
must've gone crazy trying to buy GL.
لا بد أنني جننت أثناء محاولتي شراء GL.
He actually came up with such a filthy scheme.
لقد جاء في الواقع بمثل هذه الخطة القذرة.
Lu Xingchen must've spent a lot
لا بد أن لو شينغتشن قد أنفق الكثير
to get this contract.
للحصول على هذا العقد.
Will your husband be okay?
هل سيكون زوجك بخير؟
My bestie,
صديقتي العزيزة
we're family now.
نحن عائلة الآن.
Helping you is helping his future aunt.
مساعدتك هي بمثابة مساعدة لعمته المستقبلية.
Plus,
زائد،
the whole mess started because of him.
لقد بدأت الفوضى كلها بسببه.
He should be the one to clean it up.
ينبغي أن يكون هو من يقوم بتنظيفه.
He told me he wants to go back to GL.
لقد أخبرني أنه يريد العودة إلى GL.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
I checked the assignment I gave him.
لقد قمت بمراجعة المهمة التي أعطيتها له.
It's not finished,
لم ينتهي بعد
but he shows potential.
لكنه يظهر إمكاناته.
So you agree to let him back?
فهل توافق على السماح له بالعودة؟
Tang Baozhu, what's with that look?
تانغ باوزو، ما الأمر مع هذا المظهر؟
You've used up one of your three chances.
لقد استنفدت واحدة من الفرص الثلاث التي كانت لديك.
Love you.
أحبك.
Let me be clear.
دعني أكون واضحا.
There's no other position left except executive secretary.
لم يتبق أي منصب آخر سوى السكرتير التنفيذي.
I'll make sure
سوف اتأكد من ذلك
Secretary Lu starts tomorrow.
يبدأ السكرتير لو عمله غدًا.
Good morning, Ms. Gu.
صباح الخير، السيدة جو.
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
Gu Liusu, you're out of your mind.
جو ليوسو، أنت خارج عقلك.
How could you trust what a young boy said?
كيف يمكنك أن تثق بما قاله صبي صغير؟
=Starlit Bloom=
=ازهار النجوم=
♪But I can't escape♪
♪لكنني لا أستطيع الهروب♪
♪The memories of you♪
♪ذكرياتك♪
♪The harder I try to forget♪
♪كلما حاولت أن أنسى♪
♪The more you come back to me♪
♪كلما عدت إلي أكثر♪
♪Two hearts once in love collide and shatter into pieces♪
♪قلبان كانا في حالة حب تصادما وتحطما إلى قطع♪
♪How can I piece myself together again?♪
♪كيف يمكنني أن أجمع نفسي مرة أخرى؟♪
♪Funny, isn't it?♪
♪مضحك، أليس كذلك؟♪
♪Only after losing you did I see your love was worth keeping♪
♪فقط بعد أن فقدتك رأيت أن حبك يستحق الاحتفاظ به♪
♪I hate myself for not being brave, for not trying♪
♪أكره نفسي لعدم كوني شجاعًا، لعدم محاولتي♪
♪For letting you slip away into the crowd with my own hands♪
♪لأني سمحت لك بالانزلاق إلى الحشد بيدي ♪
♪Guess we just met at the wrong time♪
♪أعتقد أننا التقينا في الوقت الخطأ♪
♪What's left of our love is nothing but ashes♪
♪ما تبقى من حبنا ليس سوى رماد♪
♪Look at us♪
♪انظر إلينا♪
♪Like two planets that were never meant to meet♪
♪مثل كوكبين لم يكن من المفترض أن يلتقيا♪
♪Colliding across the sky♪
♪الاصطدام عبر السماء♪
♪At the wrong time, I found the one I loved most♪
♪في الوقت الخطأ، وجدت الشخص الذي أحببته أكثر♪
♪Does that still count as luck?♪
♪هل لا يزال هذا يعتبر حظًا؟♪
♪Look at us♪
♪انظر إلينا♪
♪Like two planets that were never meant to meet♪
♪مثل كوكبين لم يكن من المفترض أن يلتقيا♪
♪Colliding across the sky♪
♪الاصطدام عبر السماء♪
♪Maybe we were never meant to be♪
♪ربما لم يكن من المفترض أن نكون معًا♪